https://www.fishingmagic.com/our-privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Home
News
AllCatch ReportsCompetitionsEventsHeadlinesMatch FishingNews
Features
AllCarp FishingCoarse FishingDiariesFictionGame FishingHumourMy RiverOpinionPodcastsPredator FishingRoach Obsession DiarySea Fishing
Tackle & Technique
A River Campaign…Help Needed !
Game Fishing
Rod Sturdy: North to the Future.
Fish&Fly Privacy Statement Effective as of May 2018
Data Protection Changes 25th May 2018: Europe has tightened the rules on how private data is gathered, stored and used with new legislation (GDPR – General Data Protection Regulations) enforced from May 25, 2018. It’s a complicated enforcement but essentially what it means is that your rights have changed and in summary:
Your rights
You can ask for a copy of any data held about you by us free of charge.
We need to respond within 30 days.
You can ask for your information to be changed or deleted.
You can see and change all of the information we hold about you in the control panel of your forum account.
You must give active consent to receive communications (including emails).
This is why you will be receiving lots of emails from organisations asking you to re-subscribe. i.e. no more pre-ticked boxes! Please do subscribe to our Fish&Fly newsletter!
You must be able to easily take away consent (unsubscribe) to communications.
Please see the bottom of the Fish&Fly newsletter to do this.
Why and how we collect and use your personal information
Fish & Fly recognises the importance of protecting your personal information, however, in order for our systems to act as forums based on electronic correspondence between individuals we need each person to create a unique online account. By its very nature this means that some personal data must be collected and stored. By collecting this data Fish&Fly has the following responsibilities:
We must safeguard your information and keep it secure.
All of our websites are hosted on SSL secure domains (starting with https://). This means all traffic between you and us is encrypted. The web hosting is provided by a recognised hosting provider who have their own in house security safeguards.
We should only gather and store what we need.
When you subscribe to any of the Fish&Fly forums the only private data we ask for is your first name, second name and email address. In the past we have asked for your home address, however, this information has now been deleted as is unnecessary for what we do. At registration we do ask your opinions on fishing brands and tackle but this is really to identify spammers who are trying to register. At registration we ask you whether or not you would like to receive our Fish&Fly email newsletter. You can unsubscribe from this at any time.
We must make sure you know how we gather and use your personal data (if at all).
When you register you provide us with the information outlined above but also our system records the IP address that you are using. In addition cookies are added to your browser so our system knows when you are logged in and can provide the extra functions (e.g. posting comments) only members receive. We use Google analytics to track visitor numbers and to see what they are reading and how long they are spending on the website – but this is not linked to you personally – it is system wide activity only.
We need to allow you to easily unsubscribe from communications.
All of the Fish&Fly e-newsletters allow you to unsubscribe from future mailings.
Sharing of Personal Information
We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information collected from you when you register or while you use the Website, provided that such information will NOT include personally identifying information, except as specifically authorized by you or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, or under any of the other circumstances set forth in our privacy policy, as may be amended from time to time. You should be aware that if Fish & Fly Ltd is requested by the police or any regulatory or governmental authority investigating suspected illegal actives, or upon receipt of a court order, to provide any personally identifying information or the contents of any email and/or information concerning your activities whilst using the Website, Fish & Fly Ltd shall do so. Also, Fish & Fly Ltd reserves the right to disclose personally identifying information to third parties where a complaint arises concerning your use of the Website, and that use is deemed by Fish & Fly Ltd to be inconsistent with these Terms and Conditions.
Contact Us and Complaints
In the event you have any complaints or suggestions regarding the management/moderation of the FishingMagic Forums these should in the first instance be sent to info @ fishandfly.com and not posted on the Forums. These will be given due consideration and if appropriate will be posted on the Forums by our Administration for discussion. For issues relating to moderation please send these, in the first instance, via private message to Admin and do not post on the forums as the posts will be removed.
- Advertisement -
Social Media Counter0FansLike1,323FollowersFollow EventsNo eventsall eventsFeature Archive Feature Archive
Select Month
December 2020  (7)
November 2020  (10)
April 2020  (1)
March 2020  (2)
February 2020  (4)
January 2020  (1)
December 2019  (1)
November 2019  (2)
October 2019  (5)
September 2019  (1)
August 2019  (3)
July 2019  (2)
June 2019  (4)
May 2019  (2)
April 2019  (2)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (3)
January 2019  (2)
December 2018  (2)
November 2018  (5)
October 2018  (5)
September 2018  (3)
August 2018  (4)
July 2018  (1)
June 2018  (3)
May 2018  (1)
April 2018  (1)
March 2018  (7)
February 2018  (2)
January 2018  (1)
December 2017  (6)
November 2017  (3)
October 2017  (4)
September 2017  (6)
August 2017  (1)
July 2017  (5)
June 2017  (2)
May 2017  (4)
April 2017  (3)
March 2017  (7)
February 2017  (7)
January 2017  (9)
November 2016  (2)
October 2016  (1)
August 2016  (15)
July 2016  (17)
June 2016  (35)
May 2016  (36)
April 2016  (33)
March 2016  (27)
February 2016  (26)
January 2016  (31)
December 2015  (24)
November 2015  (33)
October 2015  (19)
September 2015  (24)
August 2015  (33)
July 2015  (52)
June 2015  (48)
May 2015  (26)
April 2015  (23)
March 2015  (32)
February 2015  (33)
January 2015  (33)
December 2014  (24)
November 2014  (29)
October 2014  (36)
September 2014  (30)
August 2014  (33)
July 2014  (37)
June 2014  (39)
May 2014  (35)
April 2014  (41)
March 2014  (42)
February 2014  (33)
January 2014  (39)
December 2013  (38)
November 2013  (56)
October 2013  (74)
September 2013  (54)
August 2013  (60)
July 2013  (91)
June 2013  (63)
May 2013  (68)
April 2013  (60)
March 2013  (62)
February 2013  (62)
January 2013  (69)
December 2012  (67)
November 2012  (73)
October 2012  (79)
September 2012  (71)
August 2012  (83)
July 2012  (92)
June 2012  (93)
May 2012  (95)
April 2012  (92)
March 2012  (70)
February 2012  (84)
January 2012  (94)
December 2011  (81)
November 2011  (84)
October 2011  (69)
September 2011  (68)
August 2011  (42)
July 2011  (55)
June 2011  (25)
May 2011  (11)
April 2011  (15)
March 2011  (24)
February 2011  (22)
January 2011  (29)
December 2010  (34)
November 2010  (31)
October 2010  (40)
September 2010  (35)
August 2010  (37)
July 2010  (37)
June 2010  (38)
May 2010  (31)
April 2010  (33)
March 2010  (33)
February 2010  (23)
January 2010  (37)
December 2009  (35)
November 2009  (44)
October 2009  (34)
September 2009  (35)
August 2009  (38)
July 2009  (31)
June 2009  (37)
May 2009  (14)
April 2009  (23)
March 2009  (34)
February 2009  (26)
January 2009  (13)
December 2008  (9)
November 2008  (19)
October 2008  (13)
September 2008  (41)
August 2008  (23)
July 2008  (43)
June 2008  (67)
May 2008  (33)
April 2008  (43)
March 2008  (39)
February 2008  (40)
January 2008  (42)
December 2007  (29)
November 2007  (50)
October 2007  (51)
September 2007  (51)
August 2007  (54)
July 2007  (57)
June 2007  (64)
May 2007  (66)
April 2007  (72)
March 2007  (74)
February 2007  (67)
January 2007  (48)
December 2006  (38)
November 2006  (51)
October 2006  (51)
September 2006  (42)
August 2006  (47)
July 2006  (51)
June 2006  (64)
May 2006  (63)
April 2006  (37)
March 2006  (44)
February 2006  (42)
January 2006  (42)
December 2005  (33)
November 2005  (35)
October 2005  (36)
September 2005  (41)
August 2005  (25)
July 2005  (44)
June 2005  (50)
May 2005  (45)
April 2005  (34)
March 2005  (43)
February 2005  (40)
January 2005  (48)
December 2004  (31)
November 2004  (46)
October 2004  (43)
September 2004  (40)
August 2004  (49)
July 2004  (22)
June 2004  (31)
May 2004  (43)
April 2004  (42)
March 2004  (77)
February 2004  (47)
January 2004  (46)
December 2003  (31)
November 2003  (52)
October 2003  (56)
September 2003  (56)
August 2003  (52)
July 2003  (44)
June 2003  (37)
May 2003  (46)
April 2003  (40)
March 2003  (45)
February 2003  (45)
January 2003  (52)
December 2002  (38)
November 2002  (41)
October 2002  (56)
September 2002  (53)
August 2002  (62)
July 2002  (58)
June 2002  (47)
May 2002  (54)
April 2002  (53)
March 2002  (58)
February 2002  (58)
January 2002  (74)
December 2001  (48)
November 2001  (46)
October 2001  (53)
September 2001  (69)
August 2001  (67)
July 2001  (72)
June 2001  (57)
May 2001  (67)
April 2001  (54)
March 2001  (43)
February 2001  (57)
January 2001  (77)
December 2000  (56)
November 2000  (79)
October 2000  (67)
September 2000  (53)
August 2000  (60)
July 2000  (50)
June 2000  (55)
May 2000  (51)
April 2000  (41)
March 2000  (36)
February 2000  (25)
January 2000  (1)
Online Fishing Magazine and Forums.Contact us: info@fishingmagic.com
Our Websites
Fish and Fly
UK Fly Fishing Forums
North American Fly Fishing Forums
Salmon Fishing Forum
Sea Trout Forum
Fishing Magic
Where to Fish
iBookfishing
Thomas Turner Fishing Antiques
Member ChatRiver Lugg Decimated. December 10, 2020How did you get on? December 10, 2020A blank December 10, 2020
About Fish&Fly
Contact Us
Terms & Conditions
Our Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
© FishingMagic 2000-2018
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MoreCookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
